♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
We now return
to Hard Knocks CFL:
Training Camp
with the Toronto Argonauts.
I hope you make it.
You're real good.
No way, not as
good as you.
I hope you make it.
What're you gonna do
with all your money?
Oh, probably
just save it.
Yeah, that's
real smart.
Well, back
to my book.
Peter, I was at the park
with Stewie,
and someone stole
his tricycle.
And during, like,
the one second
I was looking down at my phone
and not at him.
Stupid thief.
It's got a vanity plate
that won't even apply to him.
Hey.
You like your reggae
watered down
and acceptable
at a wedding?
Hop on.
Ugh, can't believe somebody
stole Stewie's trike.
I only had nine payments
left on that thing.
How much do you make?
Don't worry, Lois, I'm
gonna find that tricycle.
I'll just have four to five
beers to stop the shaking,
and then I'll
go outside.
Huh, never seen that kid
around the neighborhood.
Maybe he's got something
to do with it.
Hey, kid.
You know anything
about a tricycle
that just got stolen
from the park?
No, sir, I've been
sitting here
for the last three hours
selling lemonade.
Would you like
an ice-cold glass?
Why, sure.
You couldn't have been here
for three hours on this,
the hottest day
of the year,
or the ice cubes in your
pitcher would have melted.
Ow...
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say...
Peter, Peter! We
can't arrest him.
If anything, they
can arrest you.
Hey, here's
the tricycle.
You were right,
Peter.
This kid's a thief.
We did it!
Wow, look at us.
Hey, you know,
we make a great team, guys.
Like Huey Lewis
and the Jews.
♪ We don't
need money... ♪
Sorry, the band's
breaking up.
Here you go, Stewie.
Don't bother sniffing
the seat.
It don't smell
like nothing.
Oh, yeah, my trike.
Eh, I'm kind of
over that thing.
Now I'm way into wooden
beads you move along wires.
Whoa...
Oh, yeah...
Boy, when you find
a baby's tricycle,
it feels like there's
nothing you can't do.
Man, I wish we
could quit our jobs
and solve children's
crimes full-time.
I heard you guys are
good at solving cases.
I'll give you 50 cents to
find my lucky baseball card.
Guys, we're
in business.
Oh, wait a minute, I didn't
notice you have a pierced ear.
We can't help you.
You go home
and tell your mother
she's supposed to be
a parent, not a friend.
All right, guys, this'll be
the headquarters
for our new
detective agency.
This milk crate
will be my chair,
this overturned rain barrel
will be my desk,
and this DNA evidence
centrifuge
and fingerprint scanner
will be my coatrack.
Piece of junk.
I guess all our detective
agency needs now is a name.
Well, we're detectives
solving children's crimes.
There's only one name
that makes sense.
"Dicks for Kids"?
"Dicks for Kids."
But wait, we want people
to know we're grown-ups.
Okay, "Big Dicks
For Kids."
But we don't want
to sound too old.
They're gonna think we're a
bunch of old, bald geezers.
"Big Hairy Dicks
for Kids."
How are we gonna let them
know we're "veiny"?
So, you say this gumball machine
took your dime
and didn't give you
a gumball?
That's right.
Well, I'll take care
of that.
Hand over the dime, buddy.
Come on, hand it over.
Don't make this
hard on yourself.
Wait a minute.
This gumball machine
takes quarters, not dimes.
Holy crap, it's a setup.
Time to make a quick getaway.
You were set up,
too, huh?
Yeah.
You realize that kid is plowing
both our wives right now.
So what do we got
today, boys?
Well, it seems like we got
a bit of a crime spree.
Just this morning,
we've had multiple reports
of stolen items.
Uh, couple marbles, ball
of yarn, two Wiffle ball bats.
Someday a rain'll come and wash
all this scum off the streets.
Guys, I think I've got a
lead on all these thefts.
One of the kids had
a nanny-cam hidden in his room.
Come on, let's do it
on your son's tiny bed.
Hurry, he gets home
at 3:00.
Okay, it's later than this.
Y-Yeah,
f-fast-forward ahead.
Forward. Forward.
Keep forwarding.
Is that woman
gonna be okay?
Yeah, yeah, she's fine.
We're having brunch
after this.
God, I look huge
in that bed, don't I?
You think other
guys hang out
and watch their friend's
naked gyrating butt?
It's been so long, I don't
know what other friends do.
Forwarding, forwarding,
forwarding...
And there we go.
Our thief.
Chris Gaines was Garth Brooks.
I just figured that out.
Oh, my God, Chris stole
all that stuff.
No way,
he wouldn't do that.
Peter, Chris is
on the tape.
We got to search
his bedroom.
Fine, go ahead.
But I'm telling you, it's gonna
be a bigger waste of time
than writing tough-guy dialogue
for a Jet Li movie.
This is your
last warning.
Give me back my wife.
What? Excuse me?
Give me back my wife, or
you're in a lot of trouble.
I'll kick all
your faces.
You got me?
You're kind of undoing
everything you just did
when you kicked
my ass.
I know, but I have
to say for audience.
Chris still has
an Aaron Hernandez poster up?
That's not cool.
See, there's nothing here.
Just a weird life-sized
lady doll
made out of all the stuff
that got stolen.
No!
Don't hurt Heather.
Don't hurt my girlfriend.
What the hell?!
Chris made
a sex doll?!
Your kid's got
a walk-in closet?
Two of mine gotta sleep
in the car.
Chris is still
in his room
with that disgusting
homemade sex doll.
He actually thinks
it's his girlfriend.
I know, it's weird.
It's even weirder than that
secret level in Donkey Kong.
♪ ♪
Maybe it's our fault Chris
has such a screwed-up idea
about what
a relationship is.
I mean,
let's be honest,
we're not exactly the model
of a healthy marriage.
Oh, boy, is this 'cause of
the time I pushed off of you
after sex and
bruised your boob?
No, I-I mean, when was the
last time you bought me flowers,
or-or we had
a date night?
We do stuff.
Just last week, I let
you watch me complain
after eating too
many hot wings.
Ugh!
Why did you let me
do this, Lois?!
Why?!
Okay, Peter, I got to take
the kids to school now.
Hey, Chris,
your mother wanted me
to talk to you.
Um, she doesn't think
it's healthy for you
to be spending all your time
with a homemade sex doll.
Sex doll?
I wish.
Heather hasn't even let
me get to second base.
Wh... H-Hang on.
What's second base?
Is that touching
one of the cabbages?
Yeah.
But I'm such a loser,
she'll never let me do that.
Come on, Chris,
don't sell yourself short.
You are every bit as good
as that bag of garbage.
You really think so?
Sure, I do.
And look, if you really want
to learn how to bang that thing,
there's no better teacher
than your old dad.
After all, I'm the guy
who taught old Asian people
how to get
on the subway.
Out of the way!
Nobody else matters!
All right,
you made it.
Now twirl that long hair
sticking out of your face mole.
And cough-- cough like
you never coughed before.
Okay, Chris, now, women really
dig those firemen calendars.
So we're gonna go inside
and get some sexy shots
of you doing
fireman stuff.
♪ Well, I'm hot blooded ♪
♪ Check it and see ♪
♪ I got a fever of 103 ♪
♪ Come on, baby ♪
♪ Do you do more than dance? ♪
♪ I'm hot blooded,
I'm hot blooded ♪
♪ You don't have
to read my mind... ♪
Look, Heather.
The truth is, I don't care
if we never take it
to the next level,
physically.
I just really like
spending time with you.
Wow.
I'm gonna have to write
to somebody about this.
"Dear Penthouse,
"I used to think
these letters were fake
"until my taped-together,
soccer-ball-headed girlfriend
fell in my lap."
Hey, do we still have
a magazine?
Good morning, everybody.
I think Heather will be
eating breakfast
standing up this morning,
if you know what I mean.
Peter, I thought you were
gonna take care of this.
You were supposed to make
Chris get rid of that doll.
I did take care of it.
He slept with it,
and now he'll slowly
grow to hate it
over the next 20 years.
This is all your fault.
You never listen
to anything I say.
Look, you told me
to talk to him.
I talked to him.
And now you're
nagging me about it?
God, you're more annoying than
a creative voice mail message.
♪ Joe is on a vacation
far away ♪
♪ You called him up
to talk it over ♪
♪ So many things
that you want to say ♪
♪ Leave your message
when the beep is over ♪
♪ I don't want
to miss your call ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ I already missed
your call tonight. ♪
I... I can't remember
who I called.
Oh, Lois, thank God!
Listen, I can't decide what
I want for breakfast tomorrow.
Can you make me a sample tray?
You know what, Peter?
I'm not talking
to you right now.
You screwed up
bad with Chris.
And you still
haven't apologized
for the way you
treated me earlier.
Aw, come on, Lois.
I'll make it up to you.
Maybe sooner than you know.
Oh, Peter!
They're beautiful!
You're such a sweetheart.
Read the card.
"To Heather, from Chris"?
Oh, I thought it might
have a funny riddle on it.
Oh, good, the flowers came!
We're just cocooning today
because Heather said
she's never seen TV.
So, we're starting with
season six of Becker.
I'm just gonna be
easing her in.
Lois, before you say anything.
I also got you a gift.
It's a Katherine Heigl mask for
you to wear while we have sex.
She's perfect, because
she's only sort of hot,
so there won't be this crazy
disconnect of her face
on your body, which would
totally take me out of it.
Also, it's designed so you
can wear it on your butt.
Heather, I made
your favorite cookies.
And now I want to hear
all about your day.
Hey, Lois, I heard Katherine
Heigl likes to French kiss.
Oh, my God!
Chris treats that pile of junk
better than Peter treats me!
What's the matter, Lois?
Need to get in the mood?
How about a little
help from Kenny G?
♪ ♪
I wonder if Cleveland's
gonna want his sax back.
Oh, hi, Chris.
Where have you been?
Heather and I went
for a tandem bike ride.
And then had lunch
at a gastropube.
Nope.
Huh. Sounds like fun.
What have you guys been up to?
Your father got a DVD of black
people fighting in the street.
It's not just
in the street.
Some of them are in
private residences.
Oh. Well, tomorrow, Heather
and I are going to the park
to picnic and fly kites.
And on Saturday,
she's hosting her book club,
so I have to drop by,
say something funny,
and then stay upstairs.
Wow, your plans sound
very sweet and romantic, Chris.
And how a man
should treat his woman.
Oh, Lois, your breath
smells like eggs.
Talk that way.
Chris, when you go on your
picnic tomorrow,
c-can your father
and I come with you?
Let me just ask Heather.
I know, but I think we better.
Apparently the cancer's
already in his bones.
What?
We'd love to, sounds great!
What are you doing?
You can't let him
keep thinking
that doll is real.
I know. But I just
want Peter to see
what a thoughtful man looks
like for one afternoon.
Maybe he'll learn something.
Are you sure about this?
It seems pretty extreme.
Well, I got to try something.
Peter and I used
to be so close.
But now we're like
apples and oranges.
People say we're different, but
we're really not that different.
Mm-hmm, yeah, we
both work in marketing.
We've both lost children.
We both own cars, but
we like to take the bus.
And we both cheat
at Words With Friends.
Oh, nice try!
I certainly do not!
And we're both gonna
have a moderate time
at the party tonight.
And we're not gonna count
each other's drinks.
We won't have to
because we won't be drinking.
Wow, it sure is fun going
on a picnic, isn't it, Peter?
Yeah. Will you hold
this beer bottle
while I try to kick
the top off it?
Ow! Damn it!
You moved it.
♪ Raindrops are falling
on my head ♪
♪ And just like
the guy whose feet ♪
♪ Are too big for his bed ♪
♪ Nothing seems to fit ♪
♪ Those raindrops are falling
on my head ♪
♪ They keep falling ♪
♪ Because I'm free ♪
♪ Nothing's worrying ♪
♪ Me. ♪
Close your eyes, Heather.
I've got a surprise for you.
None of your business
how much it was.
He bought her a scarf.
And it actually goes well
with her colors.
Peter, don't you see
what's going on here?!
Your son's relationship
with that doll
is better than our own marriage!
Peter?
Hey, can me and Ramon
go ride shirtless bikes?
My morning scream.
Heather's gone!
Mom! Heather's disappeared!
Have you seen her?!
No, I haven't, sweetheart.
B-But you know what?
Sometimes relationships
run their course
and come to a natural end.
This could be a sign
that it's time to move on.
Aw, and I just helped him
pick out that scarf.
I miss her so much.
I know, honey.
But if you give it
a little time,
I'm sure you'll get over her.
Just like you got over your
Hamster Dance Tourette Syndrome.
Excuse me, Mom,
could you please pass the...
♪ Dee dah Dee dah
Dee deh doh doh ♪
♪ Dee dah Dee dah doh ♪
♪ Doo doo doo doo doodle
loodle doo dah doo ♪
♪ Doo dah doodle doo
dah doodle doh doh. ♪
His brain ain't right,
but it's fun.
Hey, Chris.
I-I see you're sad.
And also sitting
on the remote.
Why did Heather leave me?!
I don't know, but sometimes
when life's got you down,
you-you got to stand
up for a second.
Like-like, just for a second.
I've never felt this sad!
Aw, looks like somebody
could use a hug.
Here we go.
Oh, no, I hit input!
Oh, no! Oh, God!
We may have to throw
away the television.
What should I do, Dad?
I don't know. Hey, where's
that girlfriend of yours?
She seems cool.
This day has Haagen-Dazs
written all over it.
Boy, he's really upset.
I can't
deal with anything
until I've had my
after-nap coffee.
I don't think guys should have
two hands on a coffee mug ever.
What?
Mmm, oh, yummy.
Don't do that, either.
J-Just-just don't do anything.
Hey, Chris.
I see you turned your hat around
so you can really get in there.
Oh, what do you care?
What does anybody care?
Why don't you come with me?
I-I've got something
to show you.
If it's the shot from Psycho
where you can see
Anne Heche's bunghole,
I've already seen it.
No, Chris, it's
something else.
Come on.
Heather? Oh, my God!
I'm sorry, Chris.
You-you did this?
I did.
I took your doll
because it's not a natural
or healthy thing for a boy
your age to have.
It looks like
you stabbed her.
Like, 50 times.
I was kind of jealous of it, so
I guess I went a little crazy.
Also, her lipstick
is all smeared.
I was having a lot
of strange feelings!
Look, Chris, I'm sorry.
You can have Heather back.
But I just want you to know,
if you ever treat a real woman
the way you treat that doll,
you're gonna make her
very happy.
Really?
Absolutely.
And I know she'll make you
very happy, too.
You know... I don't think
I need Heather anymore.
You don't?
No.
I'm glad to hear
that, Chris.
Seems like maybe
you're growing up.
Maybe.
I guess there's just
one thing left to do.
What's that?
Give me that knife.
I got to cut out the baby.
Oh, my God!
It's made of Skittles.
You want to eat the baby
together on the way home?
Yeah, I'd like that, Chris.
You know, Lois, I've been
thinking about what you said.
And I did learn
a little something
from watching
Chris and Heather.
You did?
Yeah.
From now on, I am gonna be
treating you like garbage.
Oh, Peter. Thank you.
I love you, Lois.
Mom? Dad?
I want you to meet
my new girlfriend!
This is Mistress Vita.
We met on Craigslist.
No talking unless I say!
Hi, Peter.
How'd she know your name?
Thank you for watching "Family guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru
Peter, are-are you just
trying to take a knee
until the end of the show?
Peter, that's not gonna work.
You can't just...